/r/netsec is a community-curated aggregator of technical information security content. Our mission is to extract signal from the noise — to provide value to security practitioners, students, researchers, and hackers everywhere. ‎
Technical Information Security Content & Discussion
<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><strong>Overview</strong></p> <p>If you have open positions at your company for information security professionals and would like to hire from the <a href="/r/netsec">/r/netsec</a> user base, please leave a comment detailing any open job listings at your company.</p> <p>We would also like to encourage you to post internship positions as well. Many of our readers are currently in school or are just finishing their education.</p> <p>Please reserve top level comments for those posting open positions.</p> <p><strong>Rules &amp; Guidelines</strong></p> <p>Include the company name in the post. If you want to be topsykret, go recruit elsewhere. Include the geographic location of the position along with the availability of relocation assistance or remote work.</p> <ul> <li>If you are a third party recruiter, you must disclose this in your posting.</li> <li>Please be thorough and upfront with the position details.</li> <li>Use of non-hr&#39;d (realistic) requirements is encouraged.</li> <li>While it&#39;s fine to link to the position on your companies website, provide the important details in the comment.</li> <li>Mention if applicants should apply officially through HR, or directly through you.</li> <li>Please clearly list citizenship, visa, and security clearance requirements.</li> </ul> <p>You can see an example of acceptable posts by <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/search?q=Information+Security+Hiring+Thread&amp;sort=new&amp;restrict_sr=on">perusing past hiring threads</a>.</p> <p><strong>Feedback</strong></p> <p>Feedback and suggestions are welcome, but please don&#39;t hijack this thread (use moderator mail instead.)</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/netsec_burn"> /u/netsec_burn </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1qn22ig/rnetsecs_q1_2026_information_security_hiring/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1qn22ig/rnetsecs_q1_2026_information_security_hiring/">[commentaires]</a></span>
/r/netsec's Q1 2026 Information Security Hiring Thread
<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Questions regarding netsec and discussion related directly to netsec are welcome here, as is sharing tool links.</p> <h1>Rules &amp; Guidelines</h1> <ul> <li>Always maintain civil discourse. Be awesome to one another - moderator intervention will occur if necessary.</li> <li>Avoid NSFW content unless absolutely necessary. If used, mark it as being NSFW. If left unmarked, the comment will be removed entirely.</li> <li>If linking to classified content, mark it as such. If left unmarked, the comment will be removed entirely.</li> <li>Avoid use of memes. If you have something to say, say it with real words.</li> <li>All discussions and questions should directly relate to netsec.</li> <li>No tech support is to be requested or provided on <a href="/r/netsec">r/netsec</a>.</li> </ul> <p>As always, the content &amp; discussion guidelines should also be observed on <a href="/r/netsec">r/netsec</a>.</p> <h1>Feedback</h1> <p>Feedback and suggestions are welcome, but don&#39;t post it here. Please send it to the moderator inbox.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/albinowax"> /u/albinowax </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1rhyn04/rnetsec_monthly_discussion_tool_thread/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1rhyn04/rnetsec_monthly_discussion_tool_thread/">[commentaires]</a></span>
r/netsec monthly discussion & tool thread
<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>NTLM-Relaying has been proclaimed dead a number of times, signing requirements for SMB and LDAP make it nearly impossible to use captured NTLM authentications anymore. However, it is still possible to relay to many webservers that do not enforce Extended Protection for Authentication (not just ADCS / ESC8).</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/seccore_gmbh"> /u/seccore_gmbh </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://seccore.at/blog/ntlmrelay1/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s46mif/making_ntlmrelaying_relevant_again_by_attacking/">[commentaires]</a></span>
Making NTLM-Relaying Relevant Again by Attacking Web Servers with WebRelayX
<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>[IDENTIFICADORES DE CASO - RASTREABILIDADE TOTAL]</p> <ul> <li>Google Issue Tracker (Principal): ID 494092970</li> <li>Google Issue Tracker (Antigo/Referência): ID 486921160</li> <li>Google Issue Tracker (Tentativa de Duplicação/Silenciamento): ID 494233438</li> <li>Samsung Mobile Security: Ticket 1-119703</li> </ul> <p>[RESUMO TÉCNICO] Este dossiê documenta uma falha crítica de segurança (Sandbox Escape &amp; Rootkit Persistence) identificada no Kernel 4.19 do Samsung A04s. A perícia prova que o ransomware EDWARD mantém persistência em memória viva, operando mesmo sob isolamento físico de rádio (RF-Kill).</p> <p>[EVIDÊNCIAS E AUDITORIA]</p> <ol> <li>AMBIENTE SAMSUNG A04s (Pasta Tracer 2.04): Telemetria de CPU e injeção de código que precedem o patch de março de 2026.</li> <li>AMBIENTE LENOVO (Pasta Lenovo sob RFQ): Auditoria realizada em estado de Air Gap (rfkill block all), provando que o exploit mantém rotinas de comunicação interna sem necessidade de rede externa ativa.</li> </ol> <p>[A FRAUDE DO VRP (Vulnerability Reward Program)] A Google e a Samsung utilizaram os 10GB de logs enviados em fevereiro para mitigar a falha silenciosamente no patch SMR-MAR-2026. Após a correção, classificaram os meus reports (IDs citados acima) como &quot;Inviáveis&quot; ou &quot;Duplicados&quot; de mim mesmo (ID 494233438), negando a autoria e a transparência pública. Exigir que o pesquisador atualize o sistema para &quot;validar&quot; o erro é uma tática de destruição de prova pericial.</p> <p>[CONTEXTO DO PESQUISADOR] Esta investigação é o resultado da resiliência de um cidadão que, enfrentando pressões sistêmicas, complexidades familiares e superando cicatrizes de abusos passados, manteve o rigor técnico acima de qualquer adversidade. A verdade não pode ser deletada por um patch silencioso.</p> <p>[ASSINATURAS] Hashes SHA-256 de integridade e logs cronológicos estão inclusos no link anexo.</p> <p><a href="https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1S5BTn5KxTmDEgrkjr2pIk3xanL05C9PG">https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1S5BTn5KxTmDEgrkjr2pIk3xanL05C9PG</a></p> <p>​[CLÁUSULA DE RETENÇÃO TÉCNICA E SEGURANÇA PÚBLICA] ​Atenção: Por motivos de segurança cibernética e ética profissional, o Protocolo Delta Sword não inclui a divulgação pública dos binários executáveis, códigos-fonte do exploit ou dumps de memória bruta (RAM). ​Motivos da Retenção: ​Complexidade e Risco: Os artefatos isolados (Ransomware EDWARD / Persistence Hooks) possuem alta capacidade de replicação e podem ser transformados em armas digitais se caírem em mãos erradas. ​Integridade da Prova: A documentação completa contém dados sensíveis da estrutura do Kernel Samsung/Exynos que, se expostos, poderiam comprometer dispositivos de milhões de usuários antes que as correções adequadas sejam validadas. ​Responsabilidade Civil: Como pesquisador, meu objetivo é o Full Disclosure da omissão corporativa, e não facilitar a disseminação de malwares. ​Protocolo de Acesso: O acesso à documentação completa, logs de telemetria bruta e binários para fins de auditoria, jornalismo investigativo ou segurança nacional será concedido estritamente sob as seguintes condições: ​Pedido Formal: Identificação clara da instituição ou órgão de imprensa. ​Reunião Técnica: Possibilidade de verificação de identidade e alinhamento técnico via videoconferência ou reunião presencial (conforme a sensibilidade do receptor). ​Compromisso de Sigilo: Assinatura de termo de responsabilidade sobre o manuseio dos binários. ​Para solicitações oficiais, utilize o canal de contato direto. A verdade será compartilhada com quem tem a competência e a ética para manuseá-la.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/PastAcanthisitta3863"> /u/PastAcanthisitta3863 </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1S5BTn5KxTmDEgrkjr2pIk3xanL05C9PG">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s4irxz/protocolo_delta_sword_full_disclosure_de/">[commentaires]</a></span>
PROTOCOLO DELTA SWORD: Full Disclosure de Persistência Zero-Day e Omissão Corporativa (Google/Samsung)
&#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Mempodipper"> /u/Mempodipper </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://slcyber.io/research-center/magento-polyshell-unauthenticated-file-upload-to-rce-in-magento-apsb25-94/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s42kqx/magento_polyshell_unauthenticated_file_upload_to/">[commentaires]</a></span>
Magento PolyShell – Unauthenticated File Upload to RCE in Magento (APSB25-94)
&#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/pi3ch"> /u/pi3ch </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://secdim.com/blog/post/dangerous-by-default-what-openclaw-cve-record-tells-us-about-agentic-ai-18022/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s3vnpm/dangerous_by_default_what_openclaw_cve_record/">[commentaires]</a></span>
Dangerous by Default: What OpenClaw CVE Record Tells Us About Agentic AI
&#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/AlmondOffSec"> /u/AlmondOffSec </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.mdsec.co.uk/2026/03/disabling-security-features-in-a-locked-bios/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s4l9k8/disabling_security_features_in_a_locked_bios/">[commentaires]</a></span>
Disabling Security Features in a Locked BIOS
&#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/anvilventures"> /u/anvilventures </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.anvilsecure.com/blog/exploiting-aql-injection-vulnerabilities-in-arangodb.html">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s4cvuj/exploiting_aql_injection_vulnerabilities_in/">[commentaires]</a></span>
Exploiting AQL Injection Vulnerabilities in ArangoDB
&#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/GonzoZH"> /u/GonzoZH </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://blog.compass-security.com/2026/03/common-entra-id-security-assessment-findings-part-1-foreign-enterprise-applications-with-privileged-api-permissions/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s42dm4/common_entra_id_security_assessment_findings_part/">[commentaires]</a></span>
Common Entra ID Security Assessment Findings – Part 1: Foreign Enterprise Applications With Privileged API Permissions
<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>In enterprise environments, identity effectively became the control plane once network perimeters broke down (e.g. zero trust, et cetera).</p> <p>I’m seeing a similar pattern emerging on the public internet via age verification and safety regulation, but with identity moving closer to the access layer itself.</p> <p>Not just: “Are you over 18?”</p> <p>But: identity assertions are becoming part of how access is granted at the OS/device/app store level.</p> <p>From a security perspective, this seems to introduce some new attack surfaces:</p> <ul> <li>high-value identity tokens at the OS/device level</li> <li>new trust boundaries between apps, OS, and third-party verifiers</li> <li>incentives to target device compromise or token reuse rather than account-level bypass</li> <li>potential centralisation of identity providers as enforcement points</li> </ul> <p>Questions I’m trying to think through:</p> <ul> <li>Does this effectively make identity providers the new perimeter/control plane?</li> <li>How would you model this system (closer to DRM, identity federation, or something else?)</li> <li>What are the likely failure modes if this layer becomes centralised?</li> <li>Are decentralised / on-device credentials actually viable from a security standpoint, or do they just shift the attack surface?</li> </ul> <p>Curious how people here would threat model this or where the obvious breakpoints are.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/wayne_horkan"> /u/wayne_horkan </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://horkan.com/2026/03/20/the-age-gated-internet-child-safety-identity-infrastructure-and-the-not-so-quiet-re-architecting-of-the-web">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s4bubx/the_agegated_internet_child_safety_identity/">[commentaires]</a></span>
The Age-Gated Internet: Child Safety, Identity Infrastructure, and the Not So Quiet Re-Architecting of the Web
<!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>A missing authentication check in TP-Link’s Archer NX series allows unprivileged attackers to upload firmware. The update lands as the company defends a Texas lawsuit alleging deceptive security claims.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/hayrimavi1"> /u/hayrimavi1 </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://factide.com/tp-link-patches-archer-nx-auth-bypass-still-faces-security-lawsuit/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s3kzme/tplink_patches_archer_nx_auth_bypass_still_faces/">[commentaires]</a></span>
TP-Link Patches Archer NX Auth Bypass, Still Faces Security Lawsuit
&#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/sixcommissioner"> /u/sixcommissioner </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://www.aikido.dev/blog/teampcp-deploys-worm-npm-trivy-compromise">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s3kjhf/teampcp_deploys_canisterworm_on_npm_following/">[commentaires]</a></span>
TeamPCP deploys CanisterWorm on NPM following Trivy compromise
&#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/netbiosX"> /u/netbiosX </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://ipurple.team/2026/03/25/toast-notifications/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s3edze/weaponizing_windows_toast_notifications_for/">[commentaires]</a></span>
Weaponizing Windows Toast Notifications for Social Engineering
&#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/punkpeye"> /u/punkpeye </a> <br/> <span><a href="https://glama.ai/blog/2026-03-26-the-hackers-who-tracked-my-sleep-cycle">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/netsec/comments/1s4bs6d/what_i_learned_from_a_2000_pen_test/">[commentaires]</a></span>
What I Learned from a $2,000 Pen Test